uiic.co.in 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | UIIC

## Privacy Policy

As a general rule, this website does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit the site automatically. You can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless you choose to provide such information. If  UIIC requests you to provide personal information, adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information.  
 **Cookies:**  
A cookie is a data file that certain Web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information such as a user identification code that the site uses to track the pages you have visited and use the information commercially. We do not use cookies on our web site.  
 **Email management**   
Your email address will only be recorded if you choose to communicate with us. (For example, registering email id in “Your Email for Newsletter” section, your feedback for the website etc.) It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.  
 **Collection of Personal Information:**  
If UIIC requests you for any other Personal Information you will be informed how it will be used if you choose to give it. If at any time you believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webadmin through the Feedback link.  
Note: The use of the term "Personal Information" in this privacy statement refers to any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
